If that which you obtain is victory
te ni ireru no ga shouri nara
would that which you lose be defeat?
tebanasu no wa haiboku deshou ka
A world where nobody ever hurts
daremo kizutsukanai sekai
may be no more than empty fancy
nante kireigoto kamo shirenai
But even if it is, I'll strive for it once more
sore demo mata kakete mitai
On moonlit nights like these, I'd always listen
choudo konna tsuki no yoru
to the sound of the bell as it counted the hours
toki wo tsukeru kane no ne wo kiita
while its reverberations echoed through my empty self
zankyou wa karappo no watashi
and slowly cleared up everything before me
zenbu misukashiteru you ne
Flashes of rage and vanishing cries
ikari to wameki wa matataku ma ni
pass so quickly from one person to another
hito kara hito e to te wo tasare
Like making up an unseen enemy
i mo shinai teki mo tsukuriagetara
may fuel our will to fight
tatakae to takitsukeru no
I'll continue to run as fast as my legs can go
hashiridasu sono riyuu ga
no matter how foolish my convictions may be
tatoe donna ni kudaranakutemo
Swiftly and passionately, without a shred of falsehood
atsuku hayaku hibiku kotoba
these words ring out within me
uso itsuwari no nai
So I'll listen closely at the moment I spring into motion
yakudou dake ni mimi wo sumashite