tsunaida tamashii no hi ga mune wo sasu nara
If the lamp of linked souls points towards your heart
kotoba yori motto tsuyoi hibiki ga ima kikoeru ka
Can you hear the echoes that resonate stronger than words?
roku ni me mo awasazu
We barely ever look each other in the eye
unmei ni made karande’ku
Yet our very fates have started to become intertwined
yukisaki moro kabutte’ru
Our destinations perfectly overlap
kuenai yoru wo hashire
So thread with me through the treacherous night
fukaoi shi sugita mabushisa ga
Though the glares that come from being too resolute
warui yume ni tsuzuite mo
May carry over into your nightmares
tsunaida tamashii no hi ga mune wo sasu nara
If the lamp of linked souls points towards your heart
kotoba yori motto tsuyoi hibiki ga ima kikoeru ka
Can you hear the echoes that resonate stronger than words?
deatta wake wa dou datte ii
The reason behind our fateful encounter doesn’t matter
hikitsukerarete
We are drawn together
fureta shunkan no kizu no bun dake
The more we get hurt in the moments we connect
tashika ni nareru
The clearer everything becomes