Words alone aren’t enough
kotoba ja tarinai kara
And thus the sky gave birth to songs
sora wa uta wo koboshita
Now hold on tight to your dreams!
saa nigire yume wo
Why do you continue to stand on the front lines?
hiri tsuita saizensen de hashiritsuzukeru riyuu no
The answer lies not within God, but yourself
kotae wa kamisama janaku jibun ni shika nai
You can hear a voice shouting
sakebu koe ga kikoeru
Hear
kikoeru
You can hear a voice filled with encouragement
senaka wo osu koe ga
Hear
kikoeru
A power that turns into courage
kono nakeru kurai
So strong it brings you to tears
yuuki ni naru chikara
Always
itsudemo
A power filled with warmth
atatakai chikara
Always
itsudemo
Grip it tight
tabanete
And live for this moment
ima wo ikiteikou
I’ve got your back!
Even if the stars were to fade
tatoe hoshi ga owari
Unlimited Beat
And become the tears of the heavens
ten no namida ni natte mo
Unlimited Beat
Only the memory of their life
inochi no memory dake wa
Will remain in song
uta e to nokoru
I’ve got your back!
That’s why we fight
dakara tatakaunda
Unlimited Beat
With our eyes facing skyward
bokutachi wa ue wo muite
Unlimited Beat
Carry the roaring winds
todoroke kaze yo hakobe
Over the hills of light and love
hikari to ai no oka de
Hold on tight to your dreams and never give them up!
imakoso nigire yume wo
Senki Zesshou
Symphogear