Listen up, Kabane!
I’m a Kabaneri!
I don’t give a damn!
I am...
I’ll always be me!
itsukawa suteru just as dream karino kibouzou
Someday we’ll wake from this dreamy hope
kanzenna close kootta senkou
Until then we cling to this hollow, frozen ray of light
torikagono nai kaitou
Confined within this iron cage
kikaiteki kanjyouni akita life
What meaning can we find behind our lives
hitono seijya tsumaranai
If our minds are no better than a machine’s?
Go steam ahead with your soul
Go full steam ahead
And scream it out
Let your soul scream out loud
A gleam in your fervid eye
The gleam in your fervid eyes
There ain’t no doubt
Shows not one bit of doubt
Shoot ’em off!
What you holdin’ off for?
You’re not an underdog
Keep findin’ your way
Boost ’em up!
What you holdin’ off for?
Let’s get out of control
Keep burnin’ your flame
Keep your flame burnin’ strong
FEELING
Kabaneri of the Iron Fortress: Revolt
Beginning Tracks