kuzuboshi kirameku
The stardust twinkles
yume no hoshi sa
The star of my dreams
I wanna be
ikou ze
Let’s go
Let’s go!
I...
(I...)
Wanna...
(Wanna...)
I wanna be!
(1-2-3-4!)
sekai wa kuroku somatte’ru
The world is stained in black
haku iki wa shiroi mama na no ni
But our breath remains a clear white
ima wo bukkowashi ni ikoutte
Ever since that day we vowed
yakusoku shita ano hi kara
To go smash up the present
kitto mada ma ni au hazu dakara
I’m sure we can still make it in time
I wanna be
massao na
Counted together
zetsubou to issho ni
With pallid hopelessness
himei wo age
Scream out!
tsukisasare
Sprint through!
subete ga kawaru mae ni
Before everything transitions
I...
(I...)
Wanna...
(Wanna...)
I wanna be!