We’re going to keep resisting
bokura wa koe ga kareru made
Until our voices grow hoarse
sonzai tsuzukeru
When we look around, there’s nothing but hollow happiness
me wo samaseba sanjuupon no hikari no taba no
Simulated by these vibrant distractions
iiwaketachi wo tada moteasobu jikan ga yurusu kagiri
So if this world doesn’t have room
soshite subete ga sono iiwake de
For anything else
makanaeru gurai no sekai
Is there even meaning to be found behind our caged lives?
dakara umaretekuru imi toka mo sonna ni taishitamon janai
No matter how often we try, we’ll never give up
nanbyakukai kurikaeshita ato de mou ikkai hajimatte iku
We’re sick of the ever-same superficial questions
naiteru no waratteru no tte mou takusan da yo
Only wickedness is born from this ignorant world
hottoite warui me ga haetemo sonna me de minai de
Where no one can even admit their faults
uso tsuichatte gomennasai nante iu tsumori mo nain dakara
We’re going to keep resisting
bokura wa koe ga kareru made
Until our voices grow hoarse
sonzai shitsuzukerun da yo
Averting us from the light
taiyou ni se wo muke nagara
As your voice is piercing our souls
anata no koe ga itai hodo tsukisasaru kara
We will no longer obey this world anymore
dounimo omoidoori ni susumanai
So just endure it a bit longer
sukoshi damatte yo